Mora Llovet Stok

Over 6 years of experience as a Software Engineer, I specialize in Python and I am always eager to learn new things to improve my personal and professional growth. I'm currently interested in the world of Data Analysis. After getting my Associate title I decided to expand my knowledge and continue studying what I like the most, with a hint of management.



morastok@gmail.com

+31 6 1661 9856

Almere, Netherlands

ale 📟

linkedin.com/in/morastok

github.com/MoraStok 🧲

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software Developer Self-employed

06/2022 - Present

- Worked in projects for different LATAM companies.
- Development and maintainance of web applications. Web scrapers creation to collect data from websites.

QA Engineer ActiveVideo

11/2021 - 02/2022

Hilversum. The Netherlands

- Joined ActiveVideo with a temporary contract covering a maternity leave.
- Worked in Agile Scrum team closely with developers and architects. Analyzed risk impact of developed features.
- Hands on experience with Linux Centos, Pytest Framework, Ansible, Jenkins.

Full Stack Software Engineer

J.P. Morgan Chase & Co

01/2021 - 08/2021

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Promoted from Analyst to Associate Software Engineer and joined the Structured Product Group.
- Implemented .NET components using C#. Worked with SQL Server and workload automation tools like AutoSys.

Python Software Engineer

J.P. Morgan Chase & Co

07/2018 - 01/2021

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Participated in the Code for Good hackathon and was selected to join the company as part of the Software Engineering Program.
- Worked closely with Credit traders to add and improve features to Athena, their main trade lifecycle platform.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Information Technology Management

UADE - Argentine University of the Enterprise

08/2024 - Present

Associate Degree in Software Developer UADE - Argentine University of the Enterprise

03/2018 - 12/2021

SKILLS

Python	Jira /	Agile Jenk	ins Git	Java
JavaScripl	t Ansible	e Redis	Tornado	
Splunk	MySQL	PostgreSQL	HTML	CSS
REST				

CERTIFICATES

Analyze Data to Answer Questions (06/2024 - 06/2024)

Google certificate

Process Data from Dirty to Clean (01/2024 - 01/2024)

Google certificate

Prepare Data for Exploration (10/2023 - 10/2023)

Google certificate

Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions (08/2023 - 08/2023)

Google certificate

VOLUNTEERING

Force for Good (08/2019 - 06/2020)

Salesforce and PowerBI integration for ContrataTrans, a nonprofit empowering people from the LGBT+ community to access suitable and fulfilling jobs .

Force for Good (08/2018 - 06/2019)

Software Development for AEDIN, a nonprofit in Buenos Aires that works with disabled children, particularly those with neurological impairments.

LANGUAGES

Spanish				
English				0
Dutch	0	0	0	0

INTERESTS

Books Football Movies Series Music

Video Games